Finding Aid for Samuel R. Solomon clippings files, 1948-1984
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Samuel R. Solomon clippings files
1948-1984
Solomon, Samuel R.
89288 Aa 2
Professor of political science at Eastern Michigan University. Newspaper clippings relating to the careers and activities of Michigan governors, 1948-1984.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
11 linear feet
The collection was the gift of Samuel Solomon (donor no. 7150 ).
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Samuel Solomon was a professor of political science at the Eastern Michigan University.
As a teacher of government at Eastern Michigan University, Samuel Solomon clipped articles from Michigan newspapers about Michigan governors and state government. The clippings have been arranged chronologically and provide a valuable resource on state government issues and party politics in the period of 1948 to 1984.
Subjects:
Governors--Michigan.
- Newspaper clippings, 1948-1984
  - 1948-1966 (Box 1)
  - 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - 1971-1974 (Box 4)
  - 1975 (Box 5)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 6)
  - 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - 1979 (Box 8)
  - 1980 (Box 9)
  - 1981-1982 (Box 10)
  - 1983-1984 (Box 11)